(Howard:)Isn't that
a little unreasonable?
(Sheldon:)All right, fine,
she doesn't need
(Sheldon:)her own point of view.
Now, chop-chop.
(Penny:)Come on, Amy,
show us the dress.
AMY:
Okay.
(Amy:)But I'm really stepping outside
of my comfort zone here.
(Raj:)Uh...
(Penny:)I don't think any of your
comfort zones are showing.
(Sheldon:)Yeah,
(Bernadette:)it's your third date... maybe
you could go more sexy.
(Amy:)Well, some people think
the sexiest organ is the brain.
(Penny:)No one ever bought me drinks
at a bar
(Penny:)because my brain
just popped out of my shirt.
(Amy:)Do you have any heels
higher than this?
(Amy:)He's pretty tall.
(Sheldon:)Ooh.
Ooh, tall!
(Bernadette:)Finally some details
about this mystery man.
(Penny:)Yeah, come on,
tell us more.
(Amy:)Well, I told you his name
and that he's tall.
(Amy:)What more do you need?
(Bernadette:)Did you kiss him yet?
(Amy:)Just a little peck on the lips.
(both squeal)
(Penny:)Well, we're your best friends...
give us one more detail